{
	"schema":
	{
		"examiner":"Tugbeh Emmanuel",
		"course":"HTML5 Programming",	
		"total":"20",
		"time":"10",
		"date":"2018-12-06"
	},
	"table":
	[
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following tags is used in an HTML document to instruct the browser about the version of HTML?",
			"option1":"<HTML>",
			"option2":"<!DOCTYPE HTML>",
			"option3":"<TITLE>",
			"option4":"<HEAD>",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"You need to embed an mp4 file in your HTML document. Which one of the following tags will you use for this purpose?",
			"option1":"<AUDIO>",
			"option2":"<VIDEO>",
			"option3":"<LINIK>",
			"option4":"<SPAN>",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following attributes of the <OL> tag is used to specify the style of bullet to be used in a list?",
			"option1":"reversed",
			"option2":"start",
			"option3":"type",
			"option4":"poster",
			"answer":"option3"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following code snippets can be used in the HTML document named Listings.html to associate it with a style sheet named List.css?",
			"option1":"<LINK type='text/css' rel='stylesheet' href='List.css' />",
			"option2":"<LINK type='text/css' rel='stylesheet' href='List.stylesheet' />",
			"option3":"<LINK type='text' rel='stylesheet' href='List.css' />",
			"option4":"<LINK type='text/css' rel='stylesheet' href='List.html' />",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Identify the HTML tag that is used to use an embedded style sheet in an HTML document.",
			"option1":"<HEAD>",
			"option2":"<SCRIPT>",
			"option3":"<STYLE>",
			"option4":"<TEXT>",
			"answer":"option3"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following CSS properties is used to specify some text in italics by using CSS?",
			"option1":"font-weight",
			"option2":"font-style",
			"option3":"text-indent",
			"option4":"text-align",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following CSS properties is used to control the capitalization of the text?",
			"option1":"text-transform",
			"option2":"text-decoration",
			"option3":"text-indent",
			"option4":"text-align",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following values in display property hides an element from a Web page?",
			"option1":"inline",
			"option2":"block",
			"option3":"hidden",
			"option4":"none",
			"answer":"option4"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following tags is used to add rows to a table?",
			"option1":"<TR>",
			"option2":"<TD>",
			"option3":"<THEAD>",
			"option4":"<TFOOT>",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following properties is used to control the space between the table and the content in the table?",
			"option1":"colspan",
			"option2":"border",
			"option3":"padding",
			"option4":"text-align",
			"answer":"option3"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following attributes is used to merge the cells of a column?",
			"option1":"rowspan",
			"option2":"colspan",
			"option3":"cell-spacing",
			"option4":"padding",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following attributes specifies an area around an element?",
			"option1":"srcdoc",
			"option2":"margin",
			"option3":"height",
			"option4":"scrolling",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following functions is used to display a dialog box that will enable a user to verify or accept a task?",
			"option1":"confirm()",
			"option2":"prompt()",
			"option3":"eval()",
			"option4":"parseInt()",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following attributes is used to specify the format in which the data will be submitted to the file or the URL specified in the action attribute?",
			"option1":"ID",
			"option2":"name",
			"option3":"method",
			"option4":"novalidate",
			"answer":"option3"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following attributes is used to specify that an input field must not be left empty while submitting the form?",
			"option1":"autofocus",
			"option2":"required",
			"option3":"value",
			"option4":"target",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following symbols is used to represent jQuery?",
			"option1":"#",
			"option2":"$",
			"option3":"&",
			"option4":"*",
			"answer":"option2"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following syntax should be used to select and hide all the <h1> elements in a Web page?",
			"option1":"$('h1').hide();",
			"option2":"$(h1).hide;",
			"option3":"('h1').hide;",
			"option4":"$'h3'.hide();",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Brendan Eich (author of JavaScript) wants to insert a word at the end of the content inside the <p> elements in a Web page. Which one of the following functions should he use to perform this task?",
			"option1":"append()",
			"option2":"prepend()",
			"option3":"insert()",
			"option4":"after()",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"John Resig (author of jQuery) is a Web developer. He wants to create a lightbox on a Web page. Which one of the following methods can he use to create the lightbox?",
			"option1":"colorbox();",
			"option2":"lightbox();",
			"option3":"color();",
			"option4":"light();",
			"answer":"option1"
		},
		{
			"question":"Which one of the following objects contains the information about a browser?",
			"option1":"navigator",
			"option2":"geolocation",
			"option3":"position",
			"option4":"error",
			"answer":"option1"
		}		
	]
}
